They're on a mission to bring every gnome home.
Sherlock Gnomes is a animation, family, fantasy film directed by John Stevenson.
Garden gnomes Gnomeo & Juliet recruit renown detective Sherlock Gnomes to
investigate the mysterious disappearance of other garden ornaments.
Sherlock Gnomes (voice), played by Johnny Depp.
Juliet (voice), played by Emily Blunt.
Gnomeo (voice), played by James McAvoy.
Watson (Voice), played by Chiwetel Ejiofor.
Irene (voice), played by Mary J. Blige.
Paris (voice), played by Stephen Merchant.
Sherlock Gnomes is a 2018 animated mystery comedy
film directed by John Stevenson.
A sequel to Gnomeo & Juliet (2011), it is based on the
detective character Sherlock Holmes.
James McAvoy, Emily Blunt, Maggie Smith, Michael Caine, Ashley Jensen, Matt Lucas, Stephen Merchant, and Ozzy
Osbourne reprise their roles from the first film, with Johnny Depp, Chiwetel Ejiofor, Mary J.
Blige, and Jamie Demetriou joining the cast.
The film follows garden gnomes, Gnomeo and Juliet, recruiting gnome detective Sherlock
Gnomes to find the missing ornaments from their new garden in London.
The film was released in the United States on March 23, 2018,
and in the United Kingdom on May 11, 2018.
The film received negative reviews and underperformed at the box-office,
grossing $90.5 million against a production budget of $59 million.
The film explores themes of villain, sequel, missing
person, animate statue, sherlock holmes.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.